{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296891190","data":{"timestamp":" 947296891190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296914755","data":{"timestamp":" 947296914754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296919212","data":{"timestamp":" 947296919212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296924062","data":{"timestamp":" 947296924061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296928544","data":{"timestamp":" 947296928543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296934824","data":{"timestamp":" 947296934824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296938949","data":{"timestamp":" 947296938949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296942965","data":{"timestamp":" 947296942964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296949227","data":{"timestamp":" 947296949227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296963378","data":{"timestamp":" 947296963377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296975303","data":{"timestamp":" 947296975303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" mje"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296983067","data":{"timestamp":" 947296983067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296988583","data":{"timestamp":" 947296988583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947296996460","data":{"timestamp":" 947296996460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297002247","data":{"timestamp":" 947297002247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" f485d396-2540-4b78-97ad-d590f8f7638c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297031613","data":{"timestamp":" 947297031613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 4fd18266-5f28-431e-bf6f-f960bc28e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297036881","data":{"timestamp":" 947297036881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 4fd18266-5f28-431e-bf6f-f960bc28e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297046991","data":{"timestamp":" 947297046991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 4fd18266-5f28-431e-bf6f-f960bc28e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297049189","data":{"timestamp":" 947297049188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 4fd18266-5f28-431e-bf6f-f960bc28e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297061002","data":{"timestamp":" 947297061001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" d2012646-fc5d-411a-8244-674eeab6b7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297061396","data":{"timestamp":" 947297061395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" d2012646-fc5d-411a-8244-674eeab6b7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297061640","data":{"timestamp":" 947297061639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" d2012646-fc5d-411a-8244-674eeab6b7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297061954","data":{"timestamp":" 947297061954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" d2012646-fc5d-411a-8244-674eeab6b7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297061981","data":{"timestamp":" 947297061980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" d2012646-fc5d-411a-8244-674eeab6b7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297062079","data":{"timestamp":" 947297062079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" d2012646-fc5d-411a-8244-674eeab6b7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297073403","data":{"timestamp":" 947297073403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_cho-ngu-mwi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297080807","data":{"timestamp":" 947297080807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_cho-ngu-mwi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297087523","data":{"timestamp":" 947297087523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mli-nyi-ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297104060","data":{"timestamp":" 947297104060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_za-je-ngu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297108422","data":{"timestamp":" 947297108422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-mte-mmo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297113204","data":{"timestamp":" 947297113204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mchu-be-ngu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297118506","data":{"timestamp":" 947297118506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-dha-ngo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297125526","data":{"timestamp":" 947297125525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" 50e817f2-9a4c-4667-86cb-610e06e812eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-dha-ngo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297159963","data":{"timestamp":" 947297159963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_za-je-ngu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297166018","data":{"timestamp":" 947297166018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-ti-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297172635","data":{"timestamp":" 947297172635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-mche-po"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297177284","data":{"timestamp":" 947297177284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mchu-be-ngu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" mchu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297183566","data":{"timestamp":" 947297183566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mchu-be-ngu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297188173","data":{"timestamp":" 947297188173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_cho-ngu-mwi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" mwi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297194175","data":{"timestamp":" 947297194175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_cho-ngu-mwi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297200910","data":{"timestamp":" 947297200910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-mte-mmo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" mte"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297207364","data":{"timestamp":" 947297207364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-mte-mmo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297212132","data":{"timestamp":" 947297212132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-nchi-ye"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297216694","data":{"timestamp":" 947297216693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-dha-ngo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297225590","data":{"timestamp":" 947297225590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-le-ng'o"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297230730","data":{"timestamp":" 947297230730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mli-nyi-ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947297236491","data":{"timestamp":" 947297236491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_050119"," gameId":" fdd4f898-135b-41a5-98a6-a37ca762f4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mli-nyi-ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}